Register of the Wisconsin. Justice of the Peace (Brown County): Reports, 1840-1870
Wisconsin Historical Society
Wisconsin. Justice of the Peace (Brown County): Reports, 1840-1870
Wisconsin. Justice of the Peace (Brown County)
Brown Small Series 2
0.1 c.f. (1 folder and 2 volumes)
Housed at the University of Wisconsin-Green Bay Archives and Area Research Center; owned by the Wisconsin Historical Society, Library-Archives Division
Certificates of convictions stating plaintiff and defendant, offenses, description of case, and fines levied (1853-1865, 1870); and volumes containing reports of Justices of the Peace and County Judges with summaries of cases and costs incurred in proceedings (1840-1841, 1853-1854, 1863-1867).
Contents List
- Certificates of Conviction, 1853-1865, 1870 (Folder 1)
- Reports of Justices and County Judges
  - Thomas Lee, 1840-1841 (Volume 1)
  - E. H. Ellis, 1853-1854 (Volume 1)
  - C. H. Kies - Humboldt, 1863-1867 (Volume 2)
  - E. A. Cooley, 1863-1867 (Volume 2)
  - David Agry, 1863-1867 (Volume 2)
  - J. M. Wigman, 1863 (Volume 2)
  - D. Hunt, 1864-1867 (Volume 2)
  - P. Morrison - Humboldt, Scott, 1864-1867 (Volume 2)
  - E. C. Kieler, 1865 (Volume 2)
- Petition by E. Morrow to Board to declare taxes illegal on parcel of land in Ft. Howard (pp. 18-19) (Volume 2)
- List of lands belonging to Fox and Wisconsin Improvement Company assessed in 1864 and sold for taxes (pp. 49-52) (Volume 2)